<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Design + Dev Blog]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[A blog about design and development by Andrew Paxson.]]></description>
        <link>http://localhost:3000</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:30:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:3000/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why hasn't cloud for VFX taken off?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Anybody who dared venture to a VFX conference over the last few years knows the cloud companies have been driving hard to get a piece of the VFX pie. But why hasn't it taken off?]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/articles/cloud-for-vfx</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3000/articles/cloud-for-vfx</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detailed oriented or just bikeshedding?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Being a detailed oriented person is admirable but are we really sweating the details or just spinning our wheels on the most comprehendable part of the problem?]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/articles/detailed-oriented-or-bikeshedding</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3000/articles/detailed-oriented-or-bikeshedding</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Dichotomy of Engineering for Creativity]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Building tools for creative endeavors is a unique challenge. It is a place where rigorous engineering meets the boundless creative process. The inherent contrasts and complementary forces between the systematic approach of engineering processes and the inherently chaotic nature of the creative process is a unique dichotomy that requires a unique approach.]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/articles/dichtomy-of-engineering-creativity</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3000/articles/dichtomy-of-engineering-creativity</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stop Designing and Start Prototyping.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Product design and engineering has never been more mainstream than today. All the buzzwords and processes that exist to guide good product design and engineering can sometimes lead us afar and we lose sight of the users, their problems, and our inspiration. We can lost in the details or caught up in analysis. But if there is one thing to remember its to always be prototyping.]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/articles/forget-designing-prototype</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3000/articles/forget-designing-prototype</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let's not over-hype rust.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Rust is growing in popularity and hype but we should be cautious about overselling it. I can already hear the rustaceans sharpening their claws, but hear me out. As rust evangelists, we need to be vigilant around over-hyping, or rather overselling, the language as it can be intimidating and off-putting to potential adopters.]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/articles/rust-hype</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3000/articles/rust-hype</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VIM is a good developer experience.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Anybody who has accidently stubbled into a vim process tried to quit it will naturally assume 'who the hell would use this complicated tool?!' They are not wrong but I would argue its still a great devloper experience from a designer's perspective.]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/articles/vim-design-experience</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3000/articles/vim-design-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>